Guide to the Ezra C. Stiles Collection, 1916-1953 AIS.2000.08
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ezra C. Stiles, Landscape Architecture, 1916-1948; I.
  - David Coslov, February 11, 1949 (Map-case 6, Drawer 6, Folder 9)
    Sheet 3 0f 4. Alteration to residence: elevations of front, rear, garage right side, and left side. Oversize drawing.
- Public Works, II.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series consists of two flat folders containing Stiles' work on such projects as parks, schools, and cemeteries. Notable items in the series include his design for the Clarion City Park, Shadyside Academy, Pittsburgh Garden Center, Furman University in Greenville, South Carolina, Alto-Reste Cemetery in Altoona, Pennsylvania, and the Rest Haven Cemetery in Hagerstowin, Maryland.
  - Landscape Design for Parks and Schools, 1935-1940 (Map-case 6, Drawer 6, Folder 10)
  - Landscape Design for Cemeteries, 1935-1940 (Map-case 6, Drawer 6, Folder 11)
- Industrial and Commercial Engineering, 1926-1944; III.
  Series III contains the engineering blueprints found in Stiles' home. Most of these blueprints were not designed by Stiles and share none of the characteristics of the previous two series. This series represents a number of projects ranging from road construction to industrial additions at local steel plants.
  - Hulton Road widening and relocation construction plan (Map-case 6, Drawer 6, Folder 12)
  - Hulton Road widening and relocation construction plan (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Steel Corporation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 14)
  - Bridge over the Monongahela River (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Steel Corporation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 16)
  - Carnegie Steel Corporation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 17)
  - Carnegie Steel Corporation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Steel Corporation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Steel Corporation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 20)
  - McKnight Road Renovation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 21)
  - McKnight Road Renovation (Map-case 6, Drawer 7, Folder 22)
  - McKnight Road Renovation (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 23)
  - Constitution Boulevard, Mifflin Township (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 24)
  - Allegheny County Department of Works-Standard Construction (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 25)
  - Allegheny County Department of Works-Standard Construction (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 26)
  - Robertshaw-Fulton Industries (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 27)
- Fragments, 1916-1953; IV.
  Removal of this collection from the wall of Stiles' office, where they were firmly affixed for many decades, damaged some items. This series contains such fragments, broken during removal.
  - Fragments (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 28-34)